Guide to the John Singleton Papers, 1964-1981 UA.90.F67
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Singleton Correspondence Files, XXVI.
  - October 1974 - December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - July 1974 - September 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - April 1974 - June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Draft of Working Paper, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Education's Committee on Anthropolgy and Education (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - John Singleton, 1966-1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Uducation Facility Council -- Rannjob (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Anthropology Education Brochure (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - IDEP Planning and Brochures (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Developmental Studies in Education Workshop (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - William Johnson Intro. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Seoul (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Pitt. Education Anthropology Panel -- Philadelphia Conference, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - KLC Final Report (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - IDEP- Review Reoprts, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - IDEP- Review Reoprts, - Alumni List (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - IDEP- Review Reoprts, - Planning (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Defense of Dev. Ed. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - IDEP Syllabi (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - CIES (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - CIES (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - IDEP - Project Papers - CIES (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - IDEP - Project Papers - CIES- Assessment, Project, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - IDEP - Project Papers - CIES- Project (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Papers (Box 9, Folder 5-5a)